Office of Business and Finance. Financial audits and reports. 1936-1994. UARC.0513
UCLA Library Special Collections
Office of Business and Finance. Financial audits and reports.
1936-1994
UCLA Library Special Collections
University of California, Los Angeles. Office of Business and Finance
UARC.0513
20 Linear Feet (20 cartons)
Record Series 513 contains financial audits and reports generated by the the Office of Business and Finance at the University of California, Los Angeles.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Historical note
The Office of Business and Finance at the University of California, Los Angeles is responsible for maintaining the University's financial accountability as well as budget and reporting services.
Scope and Content
Record Series 513 contains financial audits and reports generated by the the Office of Business and Finance at the University of California, Los Angeles. Files document committees, task forces, policies, internal audits, external audits, financial reviews, reports, and other financial and business activities. These materials regard academic departments, centers of study, medical centers, institutes, programs, projects, sources of private funding, taxes, payroll, budget reviews, and statuses. Additionally, the collection features administrative materials generated by the Office of Business and Finance.
This is an inactive record series; no additional University records are expected to be added.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9934669873606533
We are committed to providing ethical, inclusive, and anti-racist description of the materials we steward, and to remediating existing description of our materials that contains language that may be offensive or cause harm. We invite you to submit feedback about how our collections are described, and how they could be described more accurately, by filling out the form located on our website: Report Potentially Offensive Description in Library Special Collections.
- Jules Stein Eye Institute., 1979-1990. (Box 1)
- Biomedical amd Environmental Sciences, Lab of., 1975-1990. (Box 1)
- Law, School of., 1991. (Box 1)
- Letters and Science, School of., 1979-1991. (Box 1)
- Fowler Museum of Cultural History., 1976-1993. (Box 1)
- Neuropsychiatric Institute., 1978-1989. (Box 1)
- Nursing., 1980-1991. (Box 1)
- Obstetrics and Gynecology., 1985. (Box 1)
- Psychiatry., 1987. (Box 1)
- Psychology., 1975-1987. (Box 1)
- Public Health., 1978-1993. (Box 1)
- Radiation Oncology., 1991. (Box 1)
- Medicine, School of., 1975-1992. (Box 1)
- Faculty Compensation/Group Practice Plan., 1978-1980. (Box 1)
- Harbor/UCLA Medical Center., 1980-1991. (Box 1)
- VA Wadsworth Medical Center., 1979-1981. (Box 1)
- Howard Hughes Medical Institute., 1986-1987. (Box 1)
- Bowyer Clinic., 1987. (Box 1)
- Bovar., 1993. (Box 1)
- Theater, Film, and Television., 1972-1991. (Box 1)
- East Asian Languages and Cultures., 1983-1986. (Box 1)
- Tissue Typing Lab., 1979-1993. (Box 1)
- Brain Research Institute., 1971-1989. (Box 1)
- Chicano Studies., 1991. (Box 1)
- Southern Occupational Health Center., 1985-1986. (Box 1)
- International Students and Scholars., 1990-1993. (Box 1)
- White Mountain Research Station., 1987-1989. (Box 1)
- Recharges, revenues, and bond indentures., 1973-1991. (Box 2)
- Policies apply to campus accounts, organizations, and students, one card., 1993. (Box 2)
- POSSEE (Policy Committee on Sales, Services Activities, and Service Enterprises)., 1987-1994. (Box 2)
- POSSEE (Policy Committee on Sales, Services Activities, and Service Enterprises)., 1989-1993. (Box 3)
- Group A and B Housing System revenue., 1975-1990. (Box 3)
- Electronic Telephone and Telecommunications System revenue., 1984-1985. (Box 3)
- Parking System revenue., 1972-1986. (Box 3)
- Wooden Center revenue., 1972-1986. (Box 3)
- Student Union revenue., 1961-1986. (Box 3)
- Academic Department Support Units., 1980-1981. (Box 3)
- Resource Sharing Consortium., 1970-1990. (Box 3)
- Short Term Investment Fund (STIF) federal fund deficit., 1979-1993. (Box 3)
- Systems development., 1987. (Box 4)
- Accounting System., 1974-1975. (Box 4)
- Accounts Payable System (PAC)/Walker Interactive System., 1971-1992. (Box 4)
- Cash Register/Remittance System., 1985-1990. (Box 4)
- Financial Systems., 1975-1992. (Box 4)
- Financial System Work Group - minutes., 1981-1989. (Box 4)
- Payroll System., 1984-1994. (Box 4)
- Recharge Billing System., 1987-1991. (Box 5)
- Contract and Grant Automation Task Force., 1988-1992. (Box 5)
- Student Systems Management., 1982-1993. (Box 5)
- Billing and Receivable (BAR) System., 1988-1992. (Box 5)
- UCLA Standard Policy Manual., 1992. (Box 5)
- Relations with external auditors., 1972-1987. (Box 5)
- Establishing and reviewing funds for sales and services of educational activities., 1979-1990. (Box 6)
- Self supporting recharge activities., 1976-1989. (Box 6)
- UCLA Standard Procedures Manual., 1990-1992. (Box 6)
- Use of facilities., 1971-1985. (Box 6)
- Academic Business Officers Group (ABOG)., 1989-1991. (Box 6)
- Accounting officers meetings., 1987-1992. (Box 6)
- South Africa/Apartheid., 1986-1987. (Box 6)
- Affiliation/other agreements., 1974-1980. (Box 6)
- Alumni Association., 1978. (Box 6)
- Adding endowment income to principle., 1984-1985. (Box 6)
- Laubich Foundation., 1985. (Box 6)
- Weschler, Irving R. Memorial Fund., 1983-1986. (Box 6)
- Endowments/funds acting as endowments., 1969-1984. (Box 6)
- Faculty Center., 1980-1990. (Box 6)
- Gifts and private grants., 1974-1988. (Box 6)
- Gifts - five percent administrative fee., 1982-1989. (Box 6)
- Gifts and private grants - check processing., 1983-1984. (Box 6)
- Private support reporting requirements., 1983-1985. (Box 6)
- Adams, John M. Medal., 1983. (Box 6)
- Parvin Foundation., 1972-1976. (Box 6)
- Leo G. Reeder/American Sociological Association., 1980-1988. (Box 6)
- Robert Wood Johnson Foundation., 1981-1986. (Box 6)
- Cedars-Sinai Hospital., 1971-1974. (Box 6)
- Charles Drew Postgraduate Medical School., 1992-1993. (Box 6)
- Charles Drew Postgraduate Medical School., 1979-1991. (Box 7)
- Harbor Hospital Professional Staff Association., 1972-1976. (Box 7)
- International Student Center., 1976-1988. (Box 7)
- UCLA Foundation., 1980-1991. (Box 7)
- UCLA Council of Support Groups., 1986-1987. (Box 7)
- University membership in organizations., 1972-1991. (Box 7)
- University support groups policy., 1980-1988. (Box 7)
- James A. Doolittle Theater and UCLA Theater Group., 1985-1991. (Box 7)
- Management Research Association., 1980-1984. (Box 7)
- Audits., 1986-1989. (Box 7)
- Audits - external - Regents' auditors., 1972-1993. (Box 7)
- Regents' audits - general correspondence., 1978-1992. (Box 7)
- Regents' audits. (Box 7)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes Federal Research Project (1977-1990); County of Los Angeles Operating Agreement (1976-1992); Financial Aid for US Government (1977-1990); NCAA Intercollegiate Athletics (1986-1992); Management Research Association (1980); and Medical Faculty Compensation (1987-1988).
- Regents' audits. (Box 8)
  Includes OMBA-110 for US Government (1981-1990); UCLA Foundation Deloitie, Haskins & Sells (DH&S) Audit of Development Program (1979-1981); UCLA Foundation Compliance Review (1987-1988); and UCLA Theater Group (1986-1991).
- Regents' audit - Deloitie, Haskins & Sells (DH&S)., 1976-1980. (Box 8)
- Regents' audit - Deloitie, Haskins & Sells (DH&S)., 1980-1983. (Box 9)
- Regents' audit - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co. (PM&M)., 1984-1991. (Box 9)
- School of Public Health - indepth review., 1986-1990. (Box 10)
- Administrative Affairs Council - report of audits., 1988-1989. (Box 10)
- Audits - external - US Government (Federal)., 1972-1991. (Box 10)
- Federal audit - general correspondence., 1977-1992. (Box 10)
- Federal audit - specific areas., 1977-1992. (Box 10)
- Audits(?) (Box 10)
  Includes Campus Computing Network (1969-1984); Biology (1982-1984); Financial Aid (1990-1992); Microbiology and Immunology (1982-1988); Payroll (1981-1983); Surgery Oncology Cost Transfer (1977-1985); DOE Lab of Biomedical Environmental Science (1874-1987); NIH-Patient Care (1986-1987); Health Professions Student Loan Program (1986); and American Institute of Maghrib Studies (1985-1987).
- Federal audit - resolution/extrapolation of sample data., 1973-1986. (Box 10)
- Federal audit guidelines., 1976-1991. (Box 11)
- Audits(?) (Box 11)
  Includes NIH-NPI Dr. Louis West (1988); Academic Summer Salaries (1974-1982); Audit Process (1979-1989); Computer Utilization (1971-1981); Cost Transfers (1979-1981); Equipment Procurement (1975-1981); Equipment Screening (1976-1982); Individual Campuses (1976-1977); Labor Distribution (1976-1977); Prior Approval (1978); Recharges (1975-1981); Unclaimed Federally Funded Checks (1977-1978); and Vacation Leave (1975-1977).
- Federal audits., 1976. (Box 12)
- State of California audits., 1980. (Box 12)
- State of California audits - general correspondence., 1987-1991. (Box 12)
- Audits(?) (Box 12)
  Includes Specific Areas (1978-1989); Auditor General (1978-1992); Fiscal Controls (1987); Hayden Warehouse (1982); and Tissue Typing (1985).
- External audits - other., 1980-1992. (Box 12)
- External audits - other - general correspondence., 1982-1992. (Box 12)
- Other audits. (Box 12)
  Including Specific Areas (1993); Harbor/UCLA Tripartite (1987); Laboratory of Biomedical Environmental Sciences (1986-1987); Samuel Goldwyn Foundation (1980-1984); Payroll (1984); and Workers' Compensation (1987).
- Other audits - NCAA guidelines., 1986. (Box 12)
- Campus Foundation audit guidelines., 1988-1991. (Box 12)
- Internal audits., 1984-1993. (Box 12)
- Internal audits - general correspondence., 1964-1992. (Box 12)
- Income tax., 1980-1992. (Box 13)
- Tax status of prizes and awards., 1984-1987. (Box 13)
- Withholding information and returns., 1980-1990. (Box 13)
- Alien payments., 1971-1992. (Box 13)
- Tax identification number., 1972-1991. (Box 13)
- Loyalty oaths., 1973-1976. (Box 13)
- Patent agreements., 1963-1975. (Box 13)
- Private Practice Plans., 1984. (Box 13)
- 1099 corrections., 1985-1992. (Box 13)
- Retirement., 1985-1992. (Box 13)
- Public Employees Retirement System., 1975-1988. (Box 13)
- Phased retirement., 1991. (Box 13)
- Social Security (FICA)/Medicare., 1980-1991. (Box 13)
- UC Retirement System., 1986-1991. (Box 13)
- Severance pay plans., 1990. (Box 13)
- Salary payments., 1982-1993. (Box 13)
- Lump sum retroactive salary., 1979-1984. (Box 13)
- Summer faculty., 1989. (Box 13)
- Surepay., 1988. (Box 13)
- Unemployment insurance., 1981-1991. (Box 13)
- Union related payroll matters/supervisor's update., 1983-1984. (Box 13)
- Vacation/sick leave., 1979-1988. (Box 13)
- Worker's compensation., 1986-1989. (Box 13)
- Executive auto allowance., 1982-1993. (Box 13)
- Registration and Reg. Work Group., 1972-1993. (Box 14)
- Student Accounting Section., 1980-1987. (Box 14)
- Scholarships/grants and fellowships., 1984-1993. (Box 14)
- Tax treatment of scholarships and fellowships., 1987-1990. (Box 14)
- Graduate student health insurance., 1990. (Box 14)
- Sponsored students., 1980-1985. (Box 14)
- Taxes (other than income tax)., 1971-1993. (Box 14)
- Tax alert., 1983-1993. (Box 14)
- Taxes - State of California., 1976-1993. (Box 14)
- California - sales and use tax., 1982-1986. (Box 14)
- Los Angeles City taxes., 1969-1991. (Box 14)
- City sales and use tax., 1968-1991. (Box 14)
- Commercial Tennants Occupancy tax., 1965-1992. (Box 14)
- Property tax exemption., 1972-1985. (Box 14)
- County sales and use tax., 1946-1986. (Box 14)
- US Government., 1982-1992. (Box 14)
- Tax exempt status., 1936-1991. (Box 14)
- Unrelated business income., 1969-1991. (Box 14)
- Applicability of sales and use tax., 1976-1986. (Box 14)
- Federal excise taxes., 1987. (Box 14)
- UBIT., 1993. (Box 14)
- Work study., 1983. (Box 14)
- Record and Resource Management Section., 1979-1992. (Box 14)
- Administrative Information Systems., 1978-1992. (Box 14)
- Administrative Vice Chancellor., 1972-1993. (Box 14)
- Administrative Computing Committee., 1989-1992. (Box 14)
- Architects and Engineers., 1974-1983. (Box 14)
- Business Enterprises administrative., 1989-1993. (Box 14)
- Faculty housing assistance., 1991-1992. (Box 15)
- Leases/real estate., 1980-1993. (Box 15)
- Property Inventory Task Force., 1989-1991. (Box 15)
- Campus Activities Service Office., 1978-1991. (Box 15)
- Campus Counsel., 1974-1992. (Box 15)
- Central administrative charges., 1982-1985. (Box 15)
- Central Ticket Office., 1983-1987. (Box 15)
- Chancellor's Office., 1985-1993. (Box 15)
- IAU Conference., 1985-1986. (Box 15)
- Transforming Administration/Administrative Management Council., 1992. (Box 15)
- Child Care Center., 1976-1987. (Box 15)
- Mail Recharge Plan., 1988. (Box 15)
- Community safety., 1983-1991. (Box 15)
- Contract and grant administration., 1981-1992. (Box 15)
- Emeriti Service Center., 1991. (Box 15)
- Facilities., 1982-1992. (Box 15)
- Financial Aids Office., 1980-1989. (Box 15)
- Financial Aids Self Evaluation., 1979-1980. (Box 15)
- Graduate Division., 1987-1993. (Box 15)
- Graduate Division - tax reporting., 1992. (Box 15)
- Office of Financial Management Training., 1980-1992. (Box 15)
- Insurance and risk management., 1984-1992. (Box 15)
- Intercollegiate Athletics., 1979-1992. (Box 16)
- Tennis Center., 1979-1986. (Box 16)
- Lake Arrowhead Conference Center/Bruinwoods., 1985-1986. (Box 16)
- Student Health Service., 1994. (Box 16)
- Library., 1979-1991. (Box 16)
- Mail and Messenger., 1987-1990. (Box 16)
- Material management purchasing., 1971-1993. (Box 16)
- Medical Center., 1985-1991. (Box 16)
- Medical Center financial statements., 1987-1991. (Box 16)
- Medical malpractice insurance., 1978-1987. (Box 16)
- Hospital Financial System., 1983-1990. (Box 16)
- Clinical teaching support., 1978. (Box 16)
- Academic Computing, Office of., 1980-1993. (Box 16)
- OAC financial statements and annual reports., 1981-1992. (Box 16)
- Gateway/UCLA agreement., 1984-1989. (Box 16)
- Assistant Vice Chancellor - Business., 1985-1992. (Box 17)
- Student Affairs, Office of., 1989-1993. (Box 17)
- Parking., 1972-1992. (Box 17)
- Budget, Institutional Planning and Analysis., 1988-1992. (Box 17)
- Public Affairs., 1983-1992. (Box 17)
- Publication Services., 1989-1992. (Box 17)
- Registrar., 1984-1991. (Box 17)
- Residence Halls., 1977-1980. (Box 17)
- Campus Human Resources., 1984-1992. (Box 17)
- INS requirements., 1987. (Box 17)
- Advantage Program., 1990-1994. (Box 17)
- Storehouse., 1990-1994. (Box 18)
- Student Health Service., 1981-1992. (Box 18)
- Student Loan Office., 1980-1990. (Box 18)
- Summer Session., 1980-1987. (Box 18)
- Surplus property., 1984-1994. (Box 18)
- Telecommunications., 1989-1992. (Box 18)
- Undergraduate admissions and relations with schools., 1979-1989. (Box 18)
- University Extension., 1989-1990. (Box 18)
- Futures contract/wire transfers., 1985-1990. (Box 18)
- Vending operations., 1979-1994. (Box 18)
- Vice Chancellor - Capitol Programs., 1982-1990. (Box 18)
- Vice Chancellor - Research Programs., 1984. (Box 18)
- Vice Chancellor - Faculty Relations., 1980-1993. (Box 18)
- Student Academic Services., 1984-1989. (Box 18)
- Olympics., 1984. (Box 18)
- Transportation Services., 1983-1992. (Box 18)
- Capitol Programs/Capitol Assets., 1990-1993. (Box 18)
- Affirmative Action., 1987-1992. (Box 18)
- Business Affirmative Action/Development, small business., 1989-1992. (Box 18)
- Business Affirmative Action/Development, small business., 1989-1992. (Box 19)
- Latin Business Association., 1990-1993. (Box 19)
- ASUCLA., 1982-1993. (Box 19)
- ASUCLA - unpaid invoices., 1978-1991. (Box 19)
- Graduate Student Association., 1976-1989. (Box 19)
- ASUCLA employees integration into UCRS., 1977-1988. (Box 19)
- Appointment books., 1985-1987. (Box 19)
- Appointment books., 1988-1991. (Box 20)
- Organization charts., 1980-1992. (Box 20)
- Organization charts., 1974-1991. (Box 20)
- Student Affairs., 1980. (Box 20)
- Conflict of Interest Code., 1978-1984. (Box 20)
- Academic Planning and Budget, Office of., 1980-1992. (Box 20)
- Chancellor's Office., 1985. (Box 20)
- INS requirements., 1987. (Box 20)
- University Extension., 1991. (Box 20)
- Student Academic Services., 1982-1991. (Box 20)
- Academic Senate. (Box 20)
- Community and Government Relations, Office of., 1992. (Box 20)